nativeadbuzz.com 2015-04-05

# Privacy Policy | Native Ad Buzz

NativeAdBuzz (“we” or “us”) operates the Site located at www.NativeAdBuzz.com (the “Site”). This NativeAdBuzz Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) outlines the privacy practices associated with the Site and Promotions (as defined in the NativeAdBuzz.com Website Terms and Conditions (the “Terms and Conditions”)). You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (i) access or use the Site; and/or (ii) enter the Promotions.

If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third party for marketing purposes, please e-mail us at: contact@NativeAdBuzz.com. Please be advised that where California residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with the law.

**Personally Identifiable Information We Collect**  
We may collect your personally identifiable information when you enter the Promotion and/or request other products and/or services at the Site. We may also collect your personally identifiable information when you otherwise agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, but do not complete the applicable registration process in full. The types of personally identifiable information that we collect when you register for the Promotion include, without limitation, your: (a) name; (b) e-mail address; and (c) any and all other information requested in connection with the applicable Promotion registration process.

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information**  
By submitting your personal information on the Site or otherwise providing same to NativeAdBuzz, you agree that we may use such personal information for any lawful purposes, subject to any restrictions contained herein. We may sell, rent, lease or otherwise provide the personal information that you supply to us to any third party and we may work with other businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our users. These businesses and third parties may include, but are not limited to: (a) providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation; (b) e-mail marketers (where we collect your e-mail address); (c) telemarketers (where we collect your telephone number and where permitted by applicable law); (d) SMS text-based marketers (where we collect your mobile telephone number and where permitted by applicable law); and (e) direct marketers.

We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from user lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. The agents performing these limited functions on our behalf shall have access to our users’ personal information as needed to perform their functions for us, but we do not permit them to use your personal information for other purposes.

We will also use your personal information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request, to customize your experience on the Site and/or to contact you when necessary in connection with the Promotion and other transactions entered into by you on the Site or otherwise with NativeAdBuzz. We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our business. We may also combine the information we have gathered about you with information from other sources. We may use third parties to help us operate our business and the Site or to administer activities on our behalf.

We also reserve the right to release current or past user information in the event that we believe that the user is using, or has used, our products, services and/or Site: (i) in violation of the Terms and Conditions, the NativeAdBuzz Rules or other Promotion rules, this Privacy Policy or any other of our operating rules, policies, price schedules and other supplemental terms and conditions or documents that may be published by us from time to time; (ii) to commit unlawful acts; (iii) if such information is subpoenaed or requested pursuant to a judicial or regulatory proceeding or inquiry; (iv) if we are sold or acquired; and/or (v) when we deem it necessary or appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, and Federal Trade Commission implementing regulations. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, we reserve the right to share, sell, rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute any and all personal information with/to any third party for any and all uses permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

By registering at the Site, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR 310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the “Rule”) and applicable state do-not-call regulations. As such, notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, and/or on applicable state do-not-call lists, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing (where you have provided us with your telephone number) in accordance with the Rule and applicable state do-not-call regulations.

In addition, by submitting your personal information at the Site, you agree to receive mobile marketing (where you have provided us with your mobile telephone number) including, but not limited to, text-message based marketing, from us and our third party advertisers and marketers (where, and to the extent that, such marketing is permitted by applicable law). As such, notwithstanding that your mobile telephone number may be listed on state and/or federal Do-Not-Call registries, we retain the right to contact you via text-message based marketing in accordance with applicable state and federal law. Further, you agree that we reserve the right to share, sell, rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute your mobile telephone and other mobile data with/to any third-party for any and all non-marketing uses permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect**  
We gather end-users’ server, IP address and browser-type related information as part of the general administration of the Site (“Browser Data”). The Browser Data is comprised of the demographic, usage and/or other characteristics of Site end-users as a group without any associated personally identifiable information of Site end-users.

When an end-user visits the Site, we send a cookie and/or gif file (“Cookie”) to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the applicable end-user’s Internet browser. A Cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience at the Site. We do not use cookies to track your use of the Internet in any other way or to store any personally-identifiable information, and we do not disclose cookie information to third parties (other than as required by legal process). To find out more about Cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com. To disable and reject certain Cookies, Click Here. Even in the case where a user rejects a Cookie, he or she may still use the Site. NativeAdBuzz reserves the right to retain Cookie data indefinitely.

**Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
NativeAdBuzz reserves the right to share, rent, sell distribute and/or use the Cookie data and Browser Data for any and all lawful purposes.

**Third Party Links**  
The Site may contain links to third-party owned and/or operated websites. NativeAdBuzz is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be required to provide certain information to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and NativeAdBuzz has no responsibility or liability relating to them. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of such websites. These third party entities are independent third parties and are not affiliated with us.

Opt-Out/Unsubscribe When you submit personally identifiable information to NativeAdBuzz, you have opted-in to request that we share your personal information with third parties to receive marketing communications. When contacted by any of these companies or third parties, you should notify them directly of your choices regarding their use and sharing of your information. To opt-out of having your information shared with third parties, to unsubscribe from all NativeAdBuzz e-mail lists and to stop receiving future e-mail communications from NativeAdBuzz, please contact@NativeAdBuzz.com.

**Minors**  
We do not knowingly collect information from minors under eighteen (18) years of age. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, the Site by individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

**Security**  
All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. While we use reasonable, industry standard measures to protect personal information online and offline, no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Access to this personal information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. All of our users’ personal information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personal information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all NativeAdBuzz user personal information. Employees not adhering to our written firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

**Use of Cookies**  
We deploy both first-party and third-party cookies when consumers open or “click” a link within the emails we send pursuant to our list-management relationships or when consumers register on a partner site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing activity-based information about you, and it is designed to facilitate the receipt of targeted and relevant advertisements and site reporting on partner sites. The cookie is not associated with your email address or any other personally identifiable information.

Our cookies are used to for two purposes. First, we use cookies to better serve display advertising to consumers on partner sites; these advertisements are chosen to meet specific consumers previous web-surfing or demographic data, but the advertisements are not selected using data such as who specifically a consumer is. Secondly, we use cookies to provide partners with demographic information regarding the consumers who visit the partner’s site. Again, no personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) is included in the cookies we deploy on behalf of ourselves or others. To find out more about cookies generally, please visit http://www.cookiecentral.com.

www.NativeAdBuzz.com uses various tracking technology to collect visitor data and analyze traffic on our site. This information helps us understand customer interests and helps us improve our website. When you visit our site, the pages that you look at, and a short text file called a cookie, are downloaded to your computer. A cookie is used to store small amounts of information. This information is collected for traffic analysis only. The cookie does not contain personal details. Depending on the browser that you use, you can set your preferences to block/ refuse cookies, and/ or notify you before they are placed. NativeAdBuzz.com does not sell, give, or trade the statistics they store to any 3rd parties for data-mining or marketing purposes.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

Contact Us If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at contact@NativeAdBuzz.com
